<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on </title>
    <link>https://techpals.eu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 12:33:46 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://techpals.eu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Engineer (AWS)</title>
      <link>https://techpals.eu/careers/devops-engineer-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techpals.eu/careers/devops-engineer-aws/</guid>
      <description>We are looking for a passionate DevOps Engineer with a strong technical background and great problem solving skills to join us. The candidate will work with international development teams in fast growing tech startups.
Requirements  Hands-on experience as a dev-ops for at least 2 years Experience with AWS or any similar cloud platform is appreciated Experience with Git Experience in setting up and maintaining CI/CD for the release process Hands-on experience with configuration and infrastructure management tools (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java/Kotlin Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://techpals.eu/careers/java-kotlin-software-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techpals.eu/careers/java-kotlin-software-engineer/</guid>
      <description>We are looking for a passionate Software Engineer with a strong technical background and great problem solving skills to join us. The candidate will work with international development teams in fast growing tech startups.
Requirements  Hands-on experience as a software engineer/developer for at least 2 years (preferably in Java or Kotlin, SpringBoot) Experience designing and implementing web APIs Solid understanding of relational databases, schema design, query optimization for transactional loads, preferably on PostgreSQL Good understanding of web protocols for authentication/authorization Good understanding of Microservices Architecture and Object Oriented design patterns Experience with Git Experience with CI/CD Experience with testing frameworks Familiarity with DevOps using Terraform or similar Experience with AWS or any cloud platform is appreciated Experience with Agile/SCRUM Very good knowledge of English (speaking and writing) A strong team player attitude with excellent communication skills  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NodeJS Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://techpals.eu/careers/nodejs-software-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techpals.eu/careers/nodejs-software-engineer/</guid>
      <description>We are looking for a passionate NodeJS Software Engineer with a strong technical background and great problem solving skills to join us. The candidate will work with international development teams in fast growing tech startups.
Requirements  Hands-on experience as a software engineer/developer for at least 2 years (preferably in Node and JavaScript/TypeScript) Experience with React.js/Next.js or similar frameworks Experience designing and implementing web APIs Solid understanding of relational databases (schema design, query optimization for transactional loads) Good understanding of web protocols for authentication/authorization Good understanding of Microservices Architecture and Object Oriented design patterns Experience with Git Experience with CI/CD Experience with testing frameworks Familiarity with DevOps using Terraform or similar Experience with AWS or any cloud platform is appreciated Very good knowledge of English (speaking and writing) A strong team player attitude with excellent communication skills Experience with Agile/SCRUM  Apply</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://techpals.eu/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techpals.eu/about/</guid>
      <description>We are a tech professional services company within software development in roles such as developers, testers, project managers, product owners. We are engaging in fast growing international projects. We are big believers of teamwork and collaboration. Here you will work with hard problems, make a tangible difference, and grow! Our customers are at the forefront of both technology and working methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://techpals.eu/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techpals.eu/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
